i just want to add something to the kiki of things um you know i see a lot of judgmental
people just you know just people saying like how did she let this happen how do you
and i don't think people understand the complexity of human beings i don't think people understand
the complexity of abuse and that abuse is not necessarily something that is happening
in a linear fashion you know there are there are there are more often than not i would say
like scenarios where abuse happens in spikes it happens dynamically right and so you can have an
abusive episode and then you have a calm and that calm prepares you to just be able to get through
the next abusive episode and it really doesn't trigger you to to really start to shift until you
start to heal but then you also start to have less calms i can unequivocally say that my relationship
was emotionally abusive full stop i can also unequivocally say that i have been trained to
endure emotional abuse i'm so good at it that it didn't even feel like something
that could not be um what's what i'm looking for but something that couldn't like that we couldn't
get past or get through it wasn't until i had continued to work on you know my traumas and
continued to to try to work together on our traumas and realize that i was healing faster and then i started
to see what was taking place and understand it for what it was and be able to then excise myself from it
so please be careful about your judgments you're not in people's lives on a daily basis
you're not there to determine whether they're a victim or a volunteer so shut it up